(Sheldon:)Oh, that sounds terrible.
Why would I want to do that?
(Amy:)That's right,
they're no good without the lighter.
(Sheldon:)So much for your advice
on complimenting Penny.
Why, what happened?
(Sheldon:)She tried to rope us into going to her
acting class to see a play.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry, luckily I had the good sense
to drown that kitten in the river.
(Amy:)Sheldon, that's very rude.
She helped you with your show.
(Amy:)The right thing to do is reciprocate
by going to see her play.
(Sheldon:)Oh, so many crazy rules.
(Amy:)That better be Tootsie Rolls
you're throwing at me!
(Sheldon:)Penny.
Oh, yeah, much better.
(Raj:)What?
(Sheldon:)Amy pointed out to me that
since you did something nice for me...
(Sheldon:)...I'm obligated to do something
nice for you.